当我们违背自己的最佳利益行事时。
When we take it upon ourselves to act against our best interests.
为了我们社区的最大利益，我们必须明白这些行为是有后果的。
And the best interests of our community, we have to understand that there are consequences for those actions.
我们必须尊重权力的等级制度因为它是上帝传给我们的。
And we must respect the hierarchy of power as it is handed down to us from God.
这责任不是我自找的。
I did not ask for this responsibility.
我确实是在自己的意志下获得了权力，但这样做的动力是由一种更高的力量放在我体内的。
I did rise to power under my own volition, but the drive to do so was placed inside of me by a higher power.
吉米。
Jimmy.
今天我站在这里是上帝的旨意
It's God's will that I stand here today
认真审视一下你们的生活吧，各位。
take a hard look at your lives, people.
你相信任何事情的发生都不是出于上帝的意愿吗?
You believe that anything happens without the will of God?
如果这是上帝的意愿，他想让你们中的一个人负责…嗨,布里格斯。
If it were God's will that he wanted one of you to be in charge... Hey, Briggs.
盯紧他哥哥。
Keep a sharp eye out for the brother.
老板觉得他可以试试。
Boss thinks he might try something.
但他没有。
He did not.
上帝赐予我在这个社区发展兴趣的能力和毅力。
God blessed me with the means and the mental fortitude to grow my interests in this community.
我不仅能打开克拉克商贸局的大门，还能引进铁路。
Not only was I able to open up Clark's Mercantile and Trade, but I was able to lure in the railroad.
我知道你们很多人不同意我的方法。
Now I know that many of you do not agree with my methods.
我向你保证麦卡利斯特先生有很多机会为这个社区做点好事，但他拒绝了。
Let me assure you Mr. McCallister here's had every opportunity to do right by this community, but he's flat out refused.
吉米，你回家去吧。
Jimmy, you go on home, now.
别呆在这儿看这个。
Don't stay here and watch this.
听到了吗，儿子?
You hear me, son?
你回家去吧!
You go on home!
走吧!
Go!
“詹姆斯，”是吗?
"James," is it?
你知道今天这里发生了什么吗?
Do you understand what's happening here today?
你父亲给你上了宝贵的一课。
Well, your father is teaching you a valuable lesson.
回家了。走吧!
Go home. Go!
知道自己的位置。
Know your place.
他偷了我的东西。
He stole from me.
是的，他说了。是的，他说了!
Yes, he did. Yes, he did!
他偷了这么多好人的钱。
He stole from all these good people.
这使他成为一个罪人。
That makes him a sinner.
你知道罪人会去哪里吗?
You know where in the world sinners go?
我可以告诉你。
I can tell you.
肯定不是怀俄明州。
Sure as hell ain't Wyoming.
让他被绞死吧。
Let him hang.
开枪打死车夫。
Shoot the wagon driver.
爸爸!
Pa!
抓住他，布里格斯!
Get him, Briggs!
请帮帮我!
Please help me!
爸爸，你没事吧?
Dad, you okay?
帮助……帮助我。
Help... help me.
去叫医生。
Get the doc.
你欠我的更多。
You owe me more.
-你还好吗?-是的。
- You okay? - Yeah.
鲍比。
Bobby.
哦，天哪，不。
Oh, god, no.
全额支付。
Paid in full.
-你杀了我弟弟，你这个狗娘养的!
- You killed my brother, you son of a--!
早点把它们挂起来，这样它们就有机会在起风之前晾干。
Get these hung early so they have a chance to dry before the wind gets up.
你是要帮我还是继续看?
Are you gonna help me or just keep watching?
我喜欢看你。
I like watching you.
——是吗?你喜欢看我晾衣服吗?
- Yeah? You like watching me hang laundry?
-我喜欢看你做很多事。
- I like watching you do most things.
-我所做的一切都是为了你。
- Most things I do, I do for you.
这是真的。
That's true.
-这就是你喜欢看我的原因吧?
- Suppose that might be why you like watching me?
-我想我会喜欢看你做别的事情。
- I reckon I'd enjoy watching you do other things.
对我来说不仅仅是东西。
Not just things for me.
-比如我为我们的女儿做事?
- Like when I do things for our daughter?
——是的。你是个好妈妈。
- Yes. You're a good mother.
任何人都能看出来。
Anyone can see that.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
现在，我需要你今天做个好父亲送我们的女儿去上学。
Now, I need you to be a good father today and walk our daughter to school.
-哦，不。她已经大到可以自己走路了。
- Oh, no. She's old enough to walk herself.
她需要你。
She needs you.
我需要你。
I need you.
我今天不能遛她了因为可能要起风了而且我得把衣服晾完。
And I can't walk her today since the wind is probably gonna get up and I need to finish hanging this laundry.
我得开门了。
I have to open the store.
-那你们俩最好赶紧走，免得迟到。
- Then the two of you had best get going so you're not late.
布鲁克!
Brooke!
你得快点。
You need to hurry.
你爸爸今天送你去学校。
Your father's walking you to school today.
你为什么不能陪我走?
Why can't you walk me?
布鲁克。
Brooke.
是的,先生?
Yes, sir?
听你妈妈的话。
Listen to your mother.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
布鲁克，今天早上我有很多家务要做。
Brooke, I have too many chores to get done this morning.
所以不要争论。
So no arguing.
拿上课本，趁你们还没迟到赶紧走吧。
Grab your school books and scoot before you're both late.
我觉得你和你父亲可以一起出去走走。
I think you and your father could use a little walk together, anyway.
继续。
Go on.
-我们应该把马带走的。
- We should have taken the horse.
不。
No.
没时间给你备马鞍，送你去学校，也没时间准时回到商店开门。
There wasn't time to saddle the horse and walk you to school and be back at the store on time to open.
-我们骑马不是更快吗?
- Wouldn't we be faster on the horse?
毫无疑问。
Undoubtedly.
-那么，我们因为速度更快而节省下来的时间，不就弥补了给马上马鞍所花费的时间吗?
- Then wouldn't the time we save by being faster have made up for the time it would have taken to saddle the horse?
不。
No.
-“今天不上课，瓦莱丽小姐病了。”
- "No classes today, as Miss Valerie has taken ill."
你觉得她得了什么病?
What do you think she's ill with?
痘吗?
Pox?
可能是天花。
It's probably pox.
-你现在得走回家。我得开门了。
- You need to walk home now. I have to open the store.
-妈妈说不能让我一个人走回家。
- Mama says I'm not allowed to walk home alone.
这是无稽之谈。
That's nonsense.
-你说我应该听妈妈的话。
- You say I should listen to Mother.
这是不同的。
This is different.
-如果你让我一个人走回家，妈妈会不高兴的。
- Mama wouldn't like it if you made me walk home alone.
-坐在那里完成你的学业。
- Sit there and finish your studies.
我已经完成了学业。
I have finished my studies.
老师需要分配新的作业。
The teacher needs to assign new ones.
-那就坐在那里看书。
- Then sit there and read a book.
早上好，杰弗里斯先生。
Good morning, Mr. Jeffries.
早上好，布里格斯先生!
Good morning, Mr. Briggs!
你今天过得怎么样?
How's your day?
-很好。我能帮你什么忙吗?
- Very well. How can I help you?
-我来告诉你，布里格斯先生。
- Well, I'll tell you, Mr. Briggs.
我妈妈昨天突然想到要为这个周末的教会聚餐烤一个蛋糕。
My mother done got it in her head yesterday that she wanted to bake a cake for the church potluck this weekend.
去年，她做了一个派，但她用的苹果长在约翰逊先生的苹果树上，你知道，就是外面厕所旁边的那棵。
Now, last year, she made a pie, but the apples she used grew on Mr. Johnson's apple tree, you know, the one out back by the outhouse.
你不知道吗，这些苹果尝起来像李子一样，吃了的人都会恶心。
And wouldn't you know it, them apples tasted plum-like shit and made anybody who eat 'em sick to their gut.
我跟你说，我觉得外面厕所里的屎浸透了苹果的根部改变了普通苹果的味道。
I tell ya, I think the shit from that outhouse has soaked down to the root and changed the way a basic apple can taste.
但约翰逊先生说那是一派胡言，正因为如此，他不让妈妈再吃苹果派了，而在我看来，
But Mr. Johnson says that's a bunch of hooey, and because of that, he won't let Mama have no more apples for her apple pie, which, as far as I'm concerned,
对我和妈妈来说没什么问题，因为正如我之前提到的，苹果吃起来就像屎一样。
is fine by me and Mama because as I mentioned before, the apples taste like shit anyhow.
这让妈妈进退两难。
Well, that left a dilemma for Mama.
她不打算为这周的聚餐烤派了。
She's not going to bake pie for this week's potluck.
她能做什么呢?
What could she possibly make?
一块蛋糕。
A cake.
——没错。妈妈要烤蛋糕。
- Exactly. Mama's gonna bake a cake.
星期天做礼拜后带到教堂的聚餐上。
Bring it to the church potluck after church on Sunday.
-你需要从店里买什么东西吗，杰弗里斯先生?
- Was there something that you needed from the store, Mr. Jeffries?
-我又来了，到处乱说妈妈的事。
- There I go, blundering on around about Mama.
我忘了你不知道我为什么来。
I done forgot you don't know why I'm here.
妈妈需要一些面粉。
Mama needs some flour.
她的袋子里装满了象鼻虫，她认为这次她不能把它们都筛出来。
The sack she has is full of weevils and she don't think she can sift them all out this time.
多少磅?
How many pounds?
- 20磅的袋子就可以了。
- Just a 20-pound bag will do.
我，我没看到你在那。
I didn't, uh, I didn't see you there.
我不是真的要偷它们。
I wasn't really gonna steal 'em.
这是我和你爸爸玩的游戏。
This is a game I play with your daddy.
20磅面粉。
Twenty pounds of flour.
那是1美元和5美分。
That'll be one dollar and a nickel.
-是的，你能把它转到我母亲的账户上吗?
- Yeah, could you apply it to my mother's account?
当然。
Of course.
谢谢你，布里格斯先生。
Thank you, Mr. Briggs.
希望在周日的午宴上见到你。
Hope to see you at the luncheon on Sunday.
夫人。
Madame.
你的书读完了吗?
Have you finished reading your book?
-他想偷些糖豆。
- He tried to steal some jelly beans.
什么?
What?
那个人。
That man.
杰弗里斯先生。
Mr. Jeffries.
我抓到他拿糖豆，他又放回去了。
I caught him taking some jelly beans and he put them back.
他放回去了?
He put them back?
他做到了。
He did.
下次他来我店里的时候我会和他讨论这件事。
- I'll discuss this with him next time he's in my store.
你想要一个吗?
You want one?
不。
No.
那你想要什么?
Then what do you want?
他的手很脏。
His hands were dirty.
对不起，女士。
Pardon me, Ma'am.
我不是故意吓唬你的。
I didn't mean to frighten you.
我们不确定是否有人在家。
We weren't sure if anyone was home.
有人在家。我。
Someone is home. Me.
我能帮你什么忙吗?
How can I help you?
是的,女士。
Yes, ma'am.
首先，请允许我为我的粗鲁介绍道歉。
First, let me apologize for the rudeness of my introduction.
我叫詹姆斯·麦卡利斯特，我和我的同伴已经上路好几天了。
My name is James McCallister, and me and my companions have been on the road for several days now.
我们都累坏了，而且有点迷路了。
We're plum tired and we're more than a little lost.
同伴吗?
Companions?
是的,女士。
Yes, ma'am.
那是布茨，就在路边。
That's Boots there out by the road.
他不想骑马到那幢房子里去吓人们。
He didn't want to ride up to the house and frighten folks.
有礼貌。
Being polite.
在你后面，是大个子迈克。
And behind you, well, that's Big Mike.
万分抱歉，小姐。
Thousand pardons, miss.
我只是在后面看看有没有人在你的花园里。
I was just around back checking to see if there's anybody in your garden.
在那里?
Was there?
不。
Nope.
-你们应该直接敲门的。
- You gentlemen should have just knocked.
我们敲过门了，女士。
Well, we did knock, ma'am.
嗯，这倒是真的。
Hm, that's true.
我看见大迈克走到那扇门前敲了一下。
I saw Big Mike step up to that door and give it a rap.
我亲眼目睹了这一切。
Most definitely witnessed that with mine own.
-肯定敲得不太大声。
- Must not have knocked too loud.
我在家里肯定没听到。
I certainly didn't hear it in the house.
然而。
Nevertheless.
-好吧，如果先生们允许我把衣服放下，我很乐意告诉你们进城的方向。
- Well, if you gentlemen will just allow me a moment to put the laundry down, I will happily point you in the direction of town.
沿着这条路走大约半个小时。
It's about a half hour's walk up the road.
他们有旅馆和酒吧，还有带全新淋浴的热水浴室。
And they've got hotels and saloons, and a hot bath house with a brand new shower.
-那就太好了，女士
- Well, that would be an act of kindness, ma'am.
我们将不胜感激。
We'd be much obliged.
我丈夫随时都会来，他甚至可以亲自给你们带路。
- My husband will be along any minute, so he might even be able to show you the way himself.
你的丈夫吗?
Your husband?
是的，先生，我丈夫。
Yes, sir. My husband.
他马上就到。
He should be along any moment.
-你丈夫会是我们之前在路上看到的那个人吗?
- Would your husband happen to have been that feller we saw walking down the road earlier?
和一个小女孩散步?
Walking with a little girl?
-是的，他送我们女儿去上学。
- Yes, he was walking our daughter to school.
哦，真了不起。
Oh, ain't that somethin'.
一个成年男子送一个小女孩去上学。
A grown man walking a little girl to school.
我们当然生活在一个新时代。
We certainly live in a new age.
看起来确实是这样。
Sure does seem like it.
的确如此。
It sure does.
你说沿着这条路走半个小时就到了?
You said town's about a half an hour walk up the road?
这是正确的。
That's right.
嗯。
Hm.
你的男人肯定离开很久了如果他是陪你女儿上下学的话。
Well, your man sure been gone a long time if he was walking your daughter to school and back.
希望没发生什么事耽误他。
Sure hope nothin' happened to hold him up.
去帮他。
Go help him.
你没事吧?
You all right?
-那婊子踢了我的蛋蛋。
- The bitch kicked me in the balls.
-刚被一个手无寸铁的洗衣服的女人揍了一顿。
- Just got your ass whooped by an unarmed woman doing her laundry.
-是的。-你确定你有种?
- Yeah. - You sure you have balls?
开门，小姐。
Open up, missy.
我要进来了，不管怎样。
I'm coming in, one way or another.
还是别把我们惹毛了吧。
Might as well not piss us off in the meantime.
-女士，我觉得你误会我和那些人了。
- Madame, I think you got the wrong idea about me and the fellas.
逃跑和躲藏是没有意义的。
Ain't no sense runnin' off and hidin'.
我们不想伤害任何人。
We don't want to hurt nobody.
我们不能再到处乱逛了，要回到正途上来。
We need to quit peckerin' around and get back on the trail.
法警应该离我们不远了。
That marshal can't be too far behind.
一天，最多一天半。
A day, day and a half at most.
我们得继续前进，除非你们这些笨蛋想回到监狱里。
We need to keep moving unless you fools want to end up back in jail.
-尤斯蒂斯，闭上你的臭嘴
- Eustice, shut your damn mouth.
-现在我知道你害怕了，躲起来了。
- Now I know you're scared and you're hiding.
但如果你把头探出来，你会发现我们没有枪。
But if you just poke your head out, you'll see we don't got any guns.
我们只是想谈谈。
We just want to talk.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
继续。去找她。
Go on. Go get her.
把她带回来。
Bring her back.
-你能活下来?-是的。
- You gon' live? - Yeah.
把她带过来!
Bring her over!
很快了!
Quickly now!
她的胳膊全断了。
Her arm's all busted up.
这很好。这很好。
That's fine. That's fine.
我觉得我们一开始就不太顺利。
I feel like we got off to a bad start.
-我要把它放在你身上。
- And I'm going to put that on you.
我们第一次见面时，我做了自我介绍，不是吗?
Now, when we first met, I introduced myself, did I not?
我大声清晰地说出了自己的名字。
I said my name, loud and clear.
你可没给我同样的荣誉。丫?
You did not do me the same honor. Did ya?
我说，是吗?
I said, did ya?
-我不会给你荣誉的。
- You'll get no honor from me.
那就告诉我吧?
Tell me this then, huh?
这是你丈夫吗?嗯?
Is this your husband? Hm?
他就是我们今天早上在街上看到的那个人吗?
Is he the man we saw walking down the street this morning?
你丈夫是“科尔顿布里格斯”吗?
Is your husband the 'Colton Briggs?'
-你听说过我丈夫吗?
- Heard of my husband, have you?
-哦，我当然听说过你丈夫。
- Oh, I've certainly heard of your husband.
我们就像一家人，我和他。
We're like family, me and him.
好。
Good.
这样我就不用费心向你解释了。
That saves me the trouble of explaining it to you.
你们的世界很痛苦。
You boys are in a world of hurt.
-科尔顿·布里格斯是谁?
- Who the shit is Colton Briggs?
-你是认真的吗?科尔顿•布里格斯吗?
- Are you serious? Colton Briggs?
这是科尔顿·布里格斯的家吗?
This is Colton Briggs' place?
尤斯蒂思,安静。
Eustice, quiet.
这是正确的。
That's right.
我是他的妻子。
And I'm his wife.
你还用枪打了我的脸。
And you hit me in the face with your gun.
我的胳膊断了。
Broke my arm.
射杀了他的马。
Shot his horse.
你们把魔鬼吵醒了。
You boys have woke up the devil.
该死的，吉米。
Goddamn it, Jimmy.
你给我们带来了地狱!
You bringing hell down on us!
-我很了解你丈夫
- I absolutely know your husband, hm.
我们是老交情了。
We go way back.
事实上，我欠他人情。
In fact, I owe him a debt.
-够了。是时候回家了。
- That'll do. It's time to head home.
-妈妈没有来学校接我。
- Mama didn't come to get me from school.
-你没在学校你在这里。
- You weren't at school. You were here.
-是的，但如果我不在学校，她不会来找我吗?
- Yes, but wouldn't she come here to find me if I wasn't at school?
嘿,元帅!
Hey, Marshal!
你最好出来。
You better come on out here.
那些人是谁?
Who are those men?
这是什么?家人都好吗?
What do we got here? The family?
-也许长得像壁炉上那张照片上的父女。
- Maybe looks like the father and daughter from that picture on the mantle in there.
他们来的时候你肯定不在。
Must've been away when those fellas came through.
谢天谢地，他们没事。
Thank god they're okay.
终于有点运气了。
A little bit of luck, finally.
幸运,事实上。
Lucky, indeed.
告诉其他人到外面来。
Tell the others to come outside.
我们不应该让自己在这些人家里过得很舒服。
We shouldn't be making ourselves comfortable in these folks' home.
-伙计们，家人来了
- Hey, you guys, family's here.
他们还活着吗?
They still alive?
是的。
Yup.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
这是你们家吗?
This you folks' home?
我想替我的人道歉。
I want to apologize for my men.
我们，我们不知道没人在家我妻子在家。
We, uh, we didn't realize that no one was home and-- My wife was home.
-是的，先生，我…我再次道歉。
- Yes, sir. I... I apologize again.
我是美国法警富兰克林·贾勒特。
My name is U.S. Marshal Franklin Jarrett.
我知道你是谁。
I know who you are.
露丝在哪里?
Where's Ruth?
-恐怕你让我不知所措了，先生。
- I'm afraid you have me at a loss, sir.
我认识你吗?
Do I know you?
布里格斯吗?
Briggs?
我靠，伙计。
Holy shit, man.
我…
I...
我道歉，小姑娘。
I apologize, little lady.
那种语言不合适。
That language is not appropriate.
你有家庭吗?
You have a family?
嗯，这是一件好事。
Well, that is a good thing.
男人需要家庭。这是他的理由。
A man needs a family. It grounds him.
平衡他。这很好。
Evens him out. That is--this is good.
元帅。
Marshal.
-对不起，布里格斯，但我们得谈谈
- I'm sorry, Briggs, but we need to talk.
最好是私人的地方。
Somewhere private, preferably.
你们去帮他挖那个坑吧?
Why don't you boys go help him dig that hole?
说他不需要我们的帮助。
Says he don't want our help.
说我们应该把工作做得更好。
Says we should've been better at our jobs.
他没有错。
He ain't wrong.
去把马准备好。
Go get them horses ready.
小女人。
Little lady.
我让斯迈利热了一些炼乳，放了点红糖进去。
I had Smiley heat up some of that condensed milk and put a little brown sugar in it.
很好。让你感觉好点。
It's good. Make you feel better.
我从来不认识你妈妈。
I never knew your mama.
但我知道她是个好女人。
But I know she was a good woman.
但我认识你爸爸。
But I did know your daddy.
很多很多年前。
Years and years ago.
在这个行业里，你会遇到很多人，很多时候，这些面孔会随着时间的流逝而消失。
You meet a lot of people in this business, and the faces, a lot of times, just disappear over the years.
但不是你爸爸。
But not your daddy.
-不，先生-不是他
- No, sir. - Not him.
你爸爸是我见过的最刻薄的混蛋。
Your daddy was about the meanest son of a bitch I ever met.
请原谅我的语言，但是……我从未见过像他这样的人。
Pardon my language, but... I never met anybody like him.
他看你的眼神…就像他看穿了你。
Just the way he would look at you, just... like he was looking through you.
好像你什么都不是。
Like you were nothing.
我不是随便说的，但你爸爸是个暴力的人。
And I don't say this lightly, but y-your daddy was a violent man.
有一次我看见他射杀了三个牛仔。
I seen him shoot three cowboys one time.
这是一场公平的战斗，但我不认为他的血会增加一盎司。
Now, it was a fair fight, but I don't think his blood raised an ounce.
我不能说他是罪犯。
I can't say he was a criminal.
我不知道，但我可以说，他不是我所说的“好人”。
I don't know that, but I can say that he was not what I would call a "good man."
那时候不是。
Not back then.
你为什么要告诉我这些?
Why are you telling me this?
嗯。
Hm.
我只是想让你明白你妈妈是个多好的女人。
I guess I just want you to understand how good a woman your mama was.
她带走了我见过的最冷酷的杀手，她把他变成了一个顾家的男人。
She took the coldest killer that I've ever met, and she turned him into a family man.
照看商店。
Minding the store.
抚养一个小女人。
Raising a little lady.
你妈妈做了件好事。
That was a good thing your mama done.
-我父亲以前会杀人?
- My father used to kill people?
-是的，但那是几年前的事了。
- Yeah, but that was years ago.
-我都没见过我爸拿枪。
- I haven't even seen my father hold a gun.
-那是因为他现在是个好人了
- And that's because he's a good man now.
都是因为你妈妈的所作所为。
Because of what your mama done.
-你带着枪。你是个好人吗?
- You carry a gun. Are you a good man?
我努力去做。
I try to be.
我妈妈现在死了。
My mama's dead now.
我父亲还是个好人吗?
Is my father still a good man?
-你想让我说几句吗?
- Would you like for me to say a few words?
你说了很多话。
You said plenty of words.
没有一个能帮上忙。
None of them helped.
-有些事你应该知道。
- There's something you should know.
他们把你的谷仓弄得一团糟。
Um, them fellas left a mess in your barn.
不该让你女儿看的东西。
Not something your little girl should see.
在你让她进去之前你得把伤口清理干净。
You'll wanna clean that up before you let her go in there.
我想我们得上路了。
I reckon we'll be hitting the trail.
我以为我们只比他们晚几个小时。
I figured we're only a few hours behind 'em.
我想我很清楚他们要去哪里。
And I think I've got a pretty good idea where they're going.
-告诉我是谁干的。
- Tell me the names of the men who did this.
告诉我他们要去哪里。
Tell me where they're going.
-不，先生，我想我做不到。
- No, sir. I don't think I can do that.
我想这个世界已经有好几年没有见到以前的科尔顿·布里格斯了，我想这个世界可能会很高兴地把它留在原地。
I reckon it's been a few years since the world has seen the old Colton Briggs, and I think the world is probably pretty happy leaving that just right where it is.
告诉我是谁害死了我妻子。
Tell me the names of the men responsible for the death of my wife.
布里格斯，听听你自己说的话。
Briggs, listen to yourself.
你看到那边那个小女孩了吗?
You see that little girl over there?
她刚失去了妈妈。她现在需要父亲。
She just lost her mama. She needs her father now.
不管那个女人给你带来了什么改变，别让它们和她一起死去。
Whatever changes happened to you that that woman gave you, don't let 'em die with her.
那个小女孩需要她认识并爱着的男人。
That little girl needs the man that she knows and loves.
你知道，自从我们被授予州的地位，这片土地现在是一个新国家的一部分。
You know, ever since we were granted statehood, this here land is now part of a new country.
我们有法律。我们有正当程序。
We got laws. We got due process.
人是不会到处杀人的。
Folks just don't go around killin' other folks.
那已经不是世界了。
That ain't the world anymore.
好好照顾你的女儿。保持与上帝同在。
Keep right by your daughter. Keep right by God.
我会找到那些杀人的狗娘养的。
I will find those murderous sons of bitches.
我会抓住他们的。
I will catch 'em.
我们会把他们送上法庭，他们会被绞死。
We will take them to trial, and they will hang.
我向你保证。
I promise that to you.
照顾好你的女儿。
Take care of your daughter.
只要那个小女孩还活着，你的生活就没有复仇的余地。
As long as that little girl is alive, there's no room for vengeance in your life.
我们现在该怎么办?
What do we do now?
上床睡觉。
Go to bed.
我需要你。
I need you.
“只要她还活着。”
"As long as she's alive."
-妈妈不会喜欢你拿枪指着我的
- Mama wouldn't like you pointing that gun at me.
穿好衣服。
Get dressed.
那是裤子。没有衣服。
Those are pants. No dresses.
我们15分钟后出发。
We leave in 15 minutes.
那是妈妈的马。
That's Mama's horse.
是的。他们杀了我的。
Yeah. They killed mine.
我们得轻装上路。
We'll have to travel light.
-她不能和我们两个一起跑。
- She can't run with both of us.
如果我们想追上那些人，我们还需要一匹马。
If we're gonna catch up with those men, we're gonna need another horse.
-是的。我们会在路上找到的。
- Yeah. We'll find one along the way.
这是我们做这件事的好时机。
This is a good time for us to do this.
我在学校的老师病了。
My teacher at school is sick.
如果是天花，她可能会病好几天。
If it's pox, she could be sick for days.
她可能会死。
She could die.
他们会有一个新老师。
They'll get a new teacher.
我忘记带课本了。
I forgot my school books.
我想他们在大火中烧毁了。
I think they burned up in the fire.
我们会买新书。
We'll get new books.
我的衣服呢?
What about my clothes?
我们会买新衣服。
We'll get new clothes.
-我们为什么要烧旧的?
- Why did we burn the old ones?
-因为我们不回去了
- Because we're not going back.
我们不会回去的。
We're not going back.
等我完成我该做的事，我们就会找个新地方把你失去的一切都换回来。
As soon as I finish what I have to do, we'll find a new place and we'll replace everything you lost.
的妈妈。
'Cept Mama.
把皮带给我。
Give me the belt.
你要骂我吗?
You gonna whoop me?
把这。
Take that.
在那棵树旁边。离开小路。
Over there by that tree. Off the path.
你可以睡30分钟，而不是更长时间。
You can sleep for 30 minutes, not longer.
然后我们就吃东西，然后继续上路。
Then we'll eat, and we'll get back on trail.
我们每四个小时查一次，直到抓到他们。
We'll do that every four hours until we catch 'em.
-那些人不是越来越远了吗?
- Aren't those men getting further away?
-他们只是男人。他们也需要睡眠。
- They're only men. They need sleep, as well.
他们会等我们的。
They'll wait for us.
-但如果我们继续前进，我们可以更快到达那里。
- But if we keep going, we can be there sooner.
之前任何…-如果我们累死了，那对我们没有任何好处。
Before anything... - Won't do us any good if we get there dead tired.
或者我们的马累死了。
Or if our horse dies from exhaustion.
光找到这些人还不够。
It's not enough that we find these men.
我们得准备好杀了他们。
We need to be ready to kill 'em.
因为他们会想杀了我们。
Because they'll be meaning to kill us.
-你觉得奇怪吗?
- Did it seem strange to you?
昨晚那个小女孩?
That little girl last night?
你是什么意思?
How do you mean?
她的妈妈刚刚被杀。
Her mama had just been killed.
她就坐在尸体旁边。
She was sittin' there right next to the body.
她脸上没有一滴眼泪。
Not a tear on her face.
我都没见过那个女人。
Hell, I never even met the woman.
我哭得比她女儿还多。
I cried more about it than her own daughter.
-她可能只是被这个消息吓到了
- Well, she's probably just shocked from the news.
她妈妈刚被杀。
I mean, her mama was just killed.
她不会再回来了。
She ain't never coming back.
年轻人肯定很难理解。
Gotta be hard for any youngster to understand.
我想是的。
I suppose so.
神圣的狗屎!
Holy shit!
来吧。来吧。
Come on. Come on.
来吧。
Come on.
啊!
Argh!
我靠，儿子。
Holy shit, son.
你怎么做到的?
How'd you do that?
我的腿断了。
My leg is busted.
啊。
Ahh.
他是个射手，该死。
That one's a shooter, shit.
是那个法警。
It's that marshal.
你没朝法警开枪?
You didn't shoot the marshal?
该死的!
Goddamn it!
那混蛋在我们就位前就开始埋伏了!
That asshole started the ambush before we were in position!
我们该怎么办?
What do we do?
你看到布里格斯了吗?
Do you see Briggs?
-妈的，老大，我不知道他长什么样。
- Shit, boss, I don't know what he looks like.
-你见到他就知道了
- Oh, you'll know when you see him.
我向你保证。
I promise you that.
趴下，斯迈利!
Get down, Smiley!
哦。
Oh.
笨蛋。
Dumbass.
-让我们看看这些混蛋能走多远。
- Let's see how far them bastards get now.
老板要走了。
Boss is pulling out.
下次装弹，我们去山上。
Next reload, let's get up that hill.
我要走了。
I'm out of here.
上帝保佑我们。
God help us.
是时候离开了吗?
Is it time to leave?
-我听到从峡谷那边传来的枪声。
- I heard gunshots coming from across the canyon.
——什么时候?-十分钟前。
- When? - Ten minutes ago.
你为什么不叫醒我?
Why didn't you wake me?
没必要这么着急。
No reason to hurry.
枪声可能会让一些人加速，但他们有一个讨厌的习惯……拖别人后腿。
Gunshots might have a way of speeding some folks up, but they have a nasty habit of... slowing other folks down.
我们很快就会知道发生了什么。
We'll find out what happened soon enough.
无论哪种方式。
Either way.
我简直不敢相信。
I can't believe it.
你想告诉我刚才到底发生了什么吗?
You want to tell me what the hell just happened?
——嗯?-怎么回事，老板?
- Huh? - What the hell, boss?
前面的那些人，他们正要去山后面。
Those guys up front, they were about to go behind the hill.
如果我等着，我就看不到他们了。
I wouldn't have seen 'em if I waited.
-你应该先杀了法警。嗯?
- You were supposed to shoot the marshal first. Huh?
相反，这位天才决定开枪打死他看到的第一个人，把所有人都追进掩体，包括法警。你知道的…我费尽心思邀请科尔顿·布里格斯来找我。
Instead, genius here decides to shoot the first guy he sees, chasing everybody, including the marshal, into cover. You know... I go to enormous pains to invite Colton Briggs to come find me.
你去吧，留下一个健康的执法官。
You go ahead and leave a perfectly healthy lawman between us.
你好像在跟我作对。
It's like you're trying to work against me.
这就是这里发生的事情吗?嗯?
Is that what's happening here? Huh?
你在跟我作对?
You're working against me?
不,老板。
Nah, boss.
我支持你。
I'm with you.
我只是搞砸了。这是所有。
I just messed up. That's all.
我当然希望如此。
I certainly hope so.
因为如果那个执法官在布里格斯找到我之前阻止了他…你会付出惨重代价的。
Because if that lawman stops Briggs before he can get to me... there will be hell to pay.
毫米。
Mm.
这无关紧要。
It don't matter for nothing.
-你有什么要说的吗，老家伙?
- You got somethin' to say, old man?
如果科尔顿·布里格斯决定要来，你还不如在桌子上多放一个盘子，因为科尔顿·布里格斯要来了。
- If Colton Briggs decides he's coming, you might as well set an extra plate at the table because Colton Briggs is coming.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
有个骑手过来了。
There's a rider coming.
-杀了妈妈的人之一?
- One of the men who killed Mama?
也许是治安队的人。
Maybe one of the men from the posse.
-不管怎样，我们需要他的马。
- Either way, we need his horse.
-你会杀了他吗?-我要骑他的马
- Are you gonna kill him? - I'm gonna take his horse.
很有可能，他不喜欢我这么做。
Chances are, he won't like me doing that.
-我想妈妈不希望你杀警察
- I don't think Mama'd like you killin' no lawman.
-我不知道他是不是执法官。
- I don't know if he is a lawman.
很可能他不会停下来给我时间去问。
Chances are he won't stop and give me time to ask.
-你就不能想别的办法阻止他吗?
- Can't you think of another way to stop him?
-他会从那个方向过来。
- He'll be coming from that direction.
你站在那里让他停下来。
You stand there and get him to stop.
如何?
How?
——哭。让他为你感到难过。
- Cry. Make him feel sorry for you.
我不知道怎么做。
I don't know how.
你刚才说什么?
What did you just say?
我不知道该怎么哭。
I don't know how to cry.
现在，你听我说。
Now, you listen to me.
这个世界上的人希望你像他们一样。
People in this world expect you to act like they do.
他们希望你为他们的笑话而笑，为他们的孩子而叹息，为他们的葬礼而哭泣。
They expect you to laugh at their jokes, and sigh at their babies, and cry at their funerals.
如果你不能学会这些，他们就不会接受你。他们会把你赶出去的。
And if you can't learn to do those things, they won't accept you. They'll push you out.
现在，你想在这个世界上成功吗?
Now, do you wanna make it in this world?
回答我!你想融入吗?
Answer me! Do you wanna fit in?
那你就得学着他们的样子。
Then you're going to have to figure out how to act like them.
你还记得去年夏天牧师的女儿死了吗?
You remember last summer when the parson's daughter died?
你还记得他妻子是怎么哭的吗?
You remember how his wife cried?
“Wahhhhhhhh !Wahhhhhhhhh !”
"Wahhhhhhhh! Wahhhhhhhhh!"
哇!哇!
Wah! Wah!
-大声一点。Wahhhh !Wahhhh !
- A little louder. Wahhhh! Wahhhh!
“我的孩子!我的孩子!”
"My baby! My baby!"
——Wahhhhhhhh !Wahhhhhhhhh !
- Wahhhhhhhh! Wahhhhhhhhh!
我的孩子!我的孩子!
My baby! My baby!
-那就行了。保持下去。
- That'll have to do. Keep it up.
Wahhhhh !Wahhhhh !
Wahhhhh! Wahhhhh!
哈哈!哈哈!
Wahhh! Wahhh!
你没事吧，小姑娘?
You okay, little girl?
——Waaaahh !我的孩子!我的孩子!
- Waaaahh! My baby! My baby!
——Wahhhhhh !——婴儿吗?什么宝贝?
- Wahhhhhh! - Baby? What baby?
——什么?你想说什么?——哈哈!哈哈!
- What? What are you getting at? - Wahhh! Wahhh!
你要从马上下来。
You're gettin' off that horse.
-你应该去的。马克，他看起来很糟糕。
- You should have gone. Mark, he looked pretty bad.
什么?
What?
把你们俩丢在这里没人保护?
Leave you two here without protection?
我不是无助。
I ain't helpless.
-别开枪。-别开枪。
- Don't shoot. - Don't shoot.
是我。
It's me.
他妈的,马克。
Shit, Mark.
你吓死我们了。
You scared the hell out of us.
-你在这里做什么?
- The hell are you doing back here?
你的马呢?
Where's your horse?
问他们。
Ask them.
搞什么鬼!
What the hell!
对不起，伙计们。
I'm sorry, guys.
-布里格斯，我知道你很生气。
- Now, Briggs, I know you're upset.
见鬼，我不怪你。
Hell, I don't blame you.
但不管你认为你在做什么，你得放了他们。
But whatever you think you're doing, you need to let these boys go.
-把罗西拿过来。
- Fetch that Rossi and bring it here.
我父亲想要你的猎枪。
My father wants your shotgun.
照她说的做，格雷格。
Do what she says, Greg.
-我会把这小女孩的脑袋打得满地都是。
- I will blow this little girl's brains all over this valley.
你听到了吗?
Do you hear me?
我说过我会把她的脑袋打得满地都是。
I said I will blow her brains all over this valley.
我现在就扣动扳机。
I'll pull the trigger right now.
啊……!
Aahhh!
他哭得很厉害。
He cries pretty good.
下次我要学学他。
I'm gonna try and do it like him next time.
-你们两个都把手放在背后。
- Both of you put your hands behind your back.
这些木头够吗?
Is this enough wood?
那块木头太绿了。它需要燃烧得更热。
- That wood's too green. It needs to burn hotter.
看到顶端了吗?应该燃烧得那么热，发出红色的光。
See the tip of that? Should burn so hot it glows red.
去拿干木头来。
Fetch dry wood.
它燃烧得更热。它燃烧得更快。
It burns hotter. It burns faster.
听我说，布里格斯。
Listen to me, Briggs.
听我说。
Just listen to me.
到目前为止，你还没犯过什么不能脱身的罪。
Up till now, you haven't committed any crimes that you can't walk away from.
我知道你压力很大，失去妻子的痛苦。
I understand that you're under a lot of pressure, pain of losing your wife.
我无法想象。
I can't imagine it.
换做任何人都可能做同样的事。
Any man might have done the same thing.
做了和你一样的决定。
Made some of the same decisions that you've made.
但你马上就要越界了，再也回不来了。
But you are about to cross a line that you can't get back from.
袭击一名美国元帅，谋杀一名美国元帅，这是你以前从未遇到过的麻烦。
Assaulting a US Marshal, murdering a US Marshal, that is trouble that you have not encountered before.
你确定吗?
Are you sure about that?
-你女儿呢，布里格斯?
- What about your daughter, Briggs?
你把她当成了帮凶。
You're making her an accessory.
这些人需要治疗而你却阻止他们得到治疗
These men here need medical attention and you are preventing them from getting it.
不。你。
No. You are.
不告诉我我想知道的。
By not telling me what I want to know.
我是联邦法警。
I'm a federal marshal.
你是在让我参与谋杀。
You're asking me to participate in murder.
你在保护一个杀手。
You're protecting a killer.
来自另一个杀手。
From another killer.
正确的。
Correct.
够干了吗?
Is this dry enough?
——好。把它放在火上。
- Good. Put it on the fire.
我们很快就可以开始了。
We'll be ready to start soon.
-如果我的人出了什么事，我对天发誓，我会抓到你，亲自杀了你。
- If anything happens to my men, I swear to God, I will hunt you down and I will kill you myself.
-就像你追捕杀害我妻子的凶手一样?
- Like you hunted down the man who killed my wife?
杀了你手下的人?
The man who killed your men?
那个要为现在发生的一切负责的人?
The man responsible for everything happening right now?
我要碰碰运气。
I'll take my chances.
撕开他的衬衫。
Rip his shirt.
别碰我!
Don't you touch me!
-把棍子给他，就像我给你看的那样。
- Give him the stick like I showed you.
请……不喜欢。
Please... don't.
-詹姆斯·麦卡利斯特!——哈!
- James McCallister! - Aahh!
我叫詹姆斯·麦卡利斯特。
Name's James McCallister.
他和三个人一起，迈克尔·奥尔良，博茨·米勒和尤斯蒂斯·贝德福德。
He rides with three men, Michael Orleans and Boots Miller and Eustice Bedford.
他们都是惯犯。
They're all hardened criminals.
据说，他答应如果他们能把他从鲍威尔县的监狱里救出来就给他们一份他藏在某处的保险箱。
Word is, he promised them a share of a lockbox he's got stashed somewhere if they'd bust him out of the prison in Powell County.
他们正前往科罗拉多。
And they're headed to Colorado.
有人告诉我他有个墨西哥女孩住在他喜欢的圣罗莎镇。
Somebody told me he's got a little Mexican girl down there in a town he likes called Santa Rosa.
我追踪的线索说明他朝那个方向去了。
The trail I was on meant that he was headed that way.
我就知道这么多。我发誓。
And that's all I know about it. I swear it.
住他。
Hold him.
不,不。
No, no.
-你个狗娘养的!——啊!
- Oh, you son of a bitch! - Aaah!
-我要杀了你，你这个狗娘养的!
- I will kill you, you son of a bitch!
把熨斗拿来。
Bring me the iron.
捏住伤口两侧的肉，并把它压在一起。
Pinch the flesh on either side of the wound and push it together.
我们必须用熨斗烫一下，否则他很快就会失血过多而死。
We have to burn it with the iron or he'll bleed out soon.
-闻起来像妈妈做的兔肉
- Smells like Mama's rabbit chops.
嗯，那是威士忌。
Mm, that's the whiskey.
让我饿了。
Makes me hungry.
-嗯嗯。
- Mm-hm.
子弹使他中毒。
The bullet was poisoning him.
他现在有机会了。
He's got a chance now.
但这些人是走不出峡谷的。
But these men are not walking out of this canyon.
如果我到了圣罗莎，没有詹姆斯·麦卡利斯特，没有墨西哥女孩，没有四人帮，我就会回来，在你回来帮忙之前杀了这两个人。
If I get to Santa Rosa and there's no James McCallister, no Mexican girl, no gang of four, I will come back here and I will kill these two men before you can return with help.
然后，我会等你。
And then, I will wait for you.
不管你带多少人回来，我都会先杀了你。
And no matter how many men you bring back with you, I will kill you first.
你还没见到我，我就杀了你。
I will kill you before you even see me.
你明白吗?
Do you understand?
我们要拿走你的枪和马。
We're taking your guns and your horse.
-你得给我留匹马，布里格斯!
- You gotta leave me a horse, Briggs!
你不能拿走我的马!
You can't take my horse!
带上你妈妈的马。
Take your mother's horse.
这个很适合我。
This one suits me fine.
该死，别问我。
Damn it, don't question me.
你对你妈妈的马更有经验。
You've got more experience with your mother's horse.
她认识你。更少的惊喜。
She knows you. Fewer surprises.
现在起来。
Now get up.
我会把你的马绑在圣罗莎。
I'll leave your horse tied up in Santa Rosa.
我不是偷马贼。
I'm no horse thief.
-正义会找到你的，布里格斯
- Justice is going to find you, Briggs.
Hyah !
Hyah!
-听到了吗?去你的。
- You hear me? God damn you.
正义会抓住你的。
Justice will catch you.
——有。就像我告诉你们的。
- There. Just like I told you boys.
把她剖开，看看有什么发现。
Let's crack her open and see what we got.
哦,老天爷。
Oh, lordy.
哇!哇!
Whoo! Whoo!
"墨西哥伦敦银行"?
"El Banco Londres Y Mexico"?
-搞什么鬼?-现在安静下来。
- What the hell? - Now settle down.
怎么回事，老板?
What the hell, boss?
老大，钱在哪儿?
Where's the money, boss?
-如果我跟你过不去，我早就杀了你了。
- Now, if I was crossing you, I would have killed you already.
但我没有。
But I didn't.
只不过是一只脏老鼠。
Nothing but a dirty rat.
-你现在不太聪明了，是吧?
- You ain't too bright now, is you?
不过没关系。所以你才找到我。
But that's okay. That's why you got me.
我有头脑。
I got brains.
我的大脑告诉我，既然我们越狱了，我们就得低调一段时间。
And my brains know that since we busted out of jail, we're gonna have to lay low for a while.
至少一年左右。
At least a year or so.
你们有谁知道他们在老墨西哥花了多少钱吗?嗯?
Any of you boys got any idea what kind of money they spend down in old Mexico? Hm?
就在那里，这些钱足够我们每个人像国王一样生活多久就多久。
Right there, that's enough dinero for each of us to live like kings for as long as we need.
你们每个人都有一份，只要你们跟我在一起。
Each of you get an equal share, hm, as long as you stick with me.
或者，我们可以在这里分开，以朋友的身份分道扬镳。
Or, we can split it up here and part ways as friends.
但我要告诉你。
But I will tell you this.
那些钱，嗯……在这边一分钱都不值。
That money, well... ain't worth a nickel this side of the border.
除非你知道怎么花。
Not unless you know where to spend it.
孩子们，我是这么想的。
And boys, I do.
那个叫布里格斯的呢?
What about this Briggs fella?
-是的，我们得想办法，而且要快。
- Yeah, we're gonna have to figure that out and figure it out fast.
这都是计划的一部分。
It's all part of the plan.
-我们要等他然后像元帅那样设个埋伏吗?
- Should we wait for him and set a ambush like we did for the Marshal?
-我们不知道布里格斯离我们还有多远。
- We don't know how far behind us Briggs might be.
我们可能要在灌木丛里呆好几天。
We could be sittin' in the bush for days.
其次，布里格斯不是那种毫无准备就走进埋伏的人。
And two, Briggs ain't the type of man to walk into an ambush unprepared.
那我们怎么找到他?
Then how do we hunt him down?
我想我已经说得很清楚了。
I thought I made myself clear.
我们又不追捕任何人。
We ain't huntin' nobody.
布里格斯在追捕我们。
Briggs is huntin' us.
我们需要它做什么?
What do we need that for?
这是很好的柴火。
It's good firewood.
它在某人的坟墓上。
It was on someone's grave.
所以呢?
So?
它属于某个人。
It belongs to someone.
没有东西属于死人，因为死人什么都不需要。
Nothing belongs to the dead because the dead don't need anything.
只有活着的人才需要拥有东西。
Only the living need to possess things.
生者需要食物、水、住所、衣服、家庭、金钱和土地。
The living need food, water, shelter, clothes, family, money and land.
但死者，死者已经有人照顾过了。
But the dead, the dead've already been tended to.
一旦它们被埋在地下，它们就拥有了所需的一切。
Once they're put in the ground, they have all they need.
他们并不自私。
They're not selfish.
我喜欢死人。
I like the dead.
-我不喜欢这样。-有个警长。
- I don't like this. - There's a Sheriff.
-警长在丹佛还有两天。
- Well, the Sheriff's in Denver. Two days away.
我们切断了进城的电报线，也就是说警长要等上四天才能知道我们在这里然后出现采取行动。
We cut the telegraph lines coming into town, which means it'll be upwards of four days before any sheriff can get the news that we're here and show up and do anything about it.
那间办公室是他们关押坏人的地方，直到执法官来抓他们。
That office is where they keep the bad folks until the lawman can come pick 'em up.
-不过，像这样骑着马进城还是觉得很暴露。
- Still, feelin' mighty exposed ridin' into town like this.
-你要质疑我的每一个电话吗?
- You gonna question my every call?
现在，我需要你们在小镇边上安排一个守卫，好吗。
Now, I need you boys to set a guard at the edge of town, all right.
有人来了，告诉我一声。
Anyone rides in, you let me know.
每隔几个小时轮换一次。
And rotate every couple hours.
你们看起来都像狗屎。
You all look like dog shit.
布里格斯来之前你得好好休息否则你对我就没用了。明白吗?
I need you rested for when Briggs gets here or you're of no use to me. Understand?
女士们，我猜你们休息得很好。
And ladies, I assume you're well rested.
我需要你的服务。
I am in need of your services.
-你听到了。谁想先看?
- You heard him. Who wants first watch?
好吧，我先值第一班，但你最好四小时后来接替我。
Well, I'll take first watch, but you better come and relieve me in four hours.
你想帮我一下吗?
You want to give me a hand with this?
-那个法警说你曾经杀人。
- That marshal said you used to kill people.
-那位元帅对孩子讲话时应注意言辞。
- That marshal should guard his words when speaking to children.
啊。
Ahh.
这是真的吗?
Is it true?
是的。
Yes.
他说你放弃了。
He said you gave it up.
他说你为了妈妈放弃了。
He said you gave it up for Mama.
这是真的吗?
Is that true?
他说妈妈改变了你。
He said Mama changed you.
-我从小就知道，从小就知道。
- My entire life, even as a boy, I knew.
我知道我与众不同。
I knew I was different.
我妈妈总说我小时候不哭。
My mother always said I didn't cry as a baby.
我没有笑。
I didn't laugh.
母亲去世时，我还很小，但在她的葬礼上我没有掉一滴眼泪。
When my mother died, I was very young, but I didn't shed a tear at her funeral.
很多人都这么做了，但我没有。
Lots of folks did, but I didn't.
在成长过程中，其他孩子会玩游戏，互相开玩笑，如果他们受伤或害怕，他们就会哭。
Growing up, the other kids would play games and joke with each other, and they would cry if they got hurt or if they were scared.
我会看着他们。我很擅长假装。
And I'd watch them. I got pretty good at pretending.
不管怎样，已经足够好了。
Good enough, anyway.
假装我和其他孩子一样。
Pretending I was like the other kids.
假装我是…正常的。
Pretending I was... normal.
但就在那时，我意识到我从来不知道恐惧。
But that's when I realized I had never known fear.
在我的一生中，我见过的每个男人眼里都有恐惧。
My whole life, I'd seen fear in the eyes of every man I ever met.
期待它吧。
Come to expect it.
成年人，毫无理由地害怕。
Grown men, terrified when they had no reason to be.
我记得有一个人在找我，因为我射杀了他的几个朋友。
I remember this one man who was looking for me because I had shot a couple of his friends.
他在澡堂里赶上了我。
He caught up with me in a bathhouse.
我的手枪放在我够不着的地方，就在我衣服旁边。
My pistol's lying out of reach, next to my clothes.
我记得我看到一个男人拿枪指着一个坐在浴缸里的裸体男人，然而，他是那个发抖的人。
And I remember seeing this man holding a gun on a cold naked man sitting in a tub, and yet, he was the one shaking.
吓得不敢动。
Too scared to move.
所以，我洗完澡站起来，悄悄地走到那个男人身边，拿走了他的手枪。
So, I stood up from my bath, and I quietly walked over to the man and I took his pistol away.
然后我用枪打死了他。
And then I shot him dead with it.
他甚至都没有求饶。
He didn't even beg for his life.
即使我能识别出男人的恐惧，甚至到了我可以利用它来对付他们的地步，我可以诚实地说，我不知道那到底是什么感觉。
And even though I could recognize fear in men, even to a point where I could use it against them, I can honestly say I had no idea what it actually felt like.
就好像……我的内心是死的。
It was as if... I'd been born dead inside.
但我不在乎。因为我的内心已经死了。
But I didn't care. 'Cuz I was dead inside.
啊。
Ahh.
妈妈是怎么改变的?
How did Mama change that?
-我见到你妈妈的时候，没人介绍。
- When I met your mother, there was no introduction.
我们没有机会互相了解。
There was no getting to know each other.
我看到她的第一眼，我…
And in that first moment I saw her, I...
我感觉到了什么。
I felt something.
这是我从未有过的感觉。
Something I'd never felt before.
爱吗?
Love?
恐惧。
Fear.
怕她不和我说话。怕她不爱我。
Fear she wouldn't talk to me. Fear she wouldn't love me.
怕我不能娶她为妻。
Fear I couldn't make her my wife.
害怕失去她。
Fear of losing her.
她是我唯一害怕过的也是我唯一爱过的。
She was the only thing I ever feared and the only thing I ever loved.
-当他们告诉我妈妈死了的时候，我不知道是什么感觉。
- When they told me Mama was dead, I didn't know how to feel.
-她是你妈妈。你感到悲伤。你感到失落。
- She was your mother. You feel sad. You feel loss.
这就是你的感觉吗?
Is that how you felt?
我感到疼痛。
I felt pain.
好像我的一部分和她一起被杀了。
Like a part of me was killed with her.
你现在还有那种感觉吗?
Do you still feel like that?
妈妈死的时候，我没有任何感觉。
When Mama died, I didn't feel anything.
就好像我死了一样。
It was as if I died.
就像我迷路了。
Like I was lost.
我躺在床上，在我的房间里。
I was lying in my bed, in my room.
在我们家。
In our house.
但我觉得我再也找不到回去的路了。
But it felt like I would never find my way back to those things again.
你会的。
You will.
-你认识杀妈妈的人吗?
- Do you know the man who killed Mama?
法警跟我们说过的那个人?
The man the Marshal told us about?
詹姆斯·麦卡利斯特吗?
James McCallister?
明天，太阳升起后……
Tomorrow, after the sun comes up...
你能教我怎么射击吗?
can you teach me how to shoot?
好。
Good.
我想我会喜欢的。
I think I'd like that.
哦!婊子养的。
Ohh! Son of a bitch.
哦。哦,该死。
Oh. Oh, dammit.
-记住，闭上你的左眼。
- Now remember, keep your left eye closed.
让枪管漂过你的目标。
Let the barrel drift right above your target.
当你准备好了，轻轻地把肺里的空气都呼出来，然后让木桶掉下来。
When you're ready, gently breathe all the air out of your lungs and let the barrel fall.
计时，这样你的呼吸就会在你拍摄的时候结束。
Time it so your breath ends just as you line up your shot.
用尽呼吸，扣动扳机，不要扣动，用整只手扣动。
At the bottom of your breath, squeeze the trigger, don't pull, squeeze with your whole hand.
你的目标是帽子吗?
Were you aiming for the hat?
-就在它下面。我瞄准的是他的胸部。
- Just below it. I was aiming for his chest.
-你拉的。你没有挤。
- You pulled. You didn't squeeze.
让我们再试一次。
Let's try it again.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我能试试这把手枪吗?
Can I try the pistol?
Hyah !打击!
Hyah! Hit!
记得要挤。
Remember to squeeze.
不要拉。
Don't pull.
早上,尤斯蒂思。
Morning, Eustice.
昨晚那些火鸡笨蛋没能帮我解职。
Those turkey bungholes never relieved me of duty last night.
让我在外面坐了一晚上!
Left me sittin' out there all night!
是这样吗?
Is that so?
男孩?下来吧。
Boys? Come on down.
怎么了，老板?
What is it, boss?
尤斯蒂斯有一件委屈想跟其他帮派成员说。
Eustice here has a grievance he would like to air with the rest of the gang.
去做吧。
Go ahead.
你们两个!
You two!
你应该在四个小时后接替我的工作。
You were supposed to relieve me in my post, after four hours.
但这并没有发生。
And that didn't happen.
这是胡扯!
And that's bullshit!
-尤斯蒂斯，请接受我代表其他人最诚挚的道歉。
- Eustice, please accept my sincerest apologies on behalf of the rest of the gang.
我们真的很抱歉，对吧，孩子们?
We sure are sorry, ain't we, boys?
-你为什么不直接来接我们?
- And why didn't you just come get us?
什么?
What?
-如果我们应该代替你，你为什么不直接找我们中的一个来代替你呢?
- If we were supposed to relieve you, why didn't you just come get one of us to take your place?
——尤斯蒂思?你为什么不去找一个男孩?
- Eustice? Why didn't you just come get one of the boys?
-我不想离开岗位，你知道吗?
- Well, I-I didn't want to leave my post, you know?
我…布里格斯是个危险人物。
I... Briggs is a dangerous man.
如果他看到这里没有保安，他可能会溜进来抓我们。
And if he would've seen there was no guard, he might have snuck in here and got us.
-你没有…睡着了，是吗?
- You didn't... fall asleep, did you?
不,老板。
No, boss.
-尤斯蒂思…你不会是在骗我吧?
- Eustice... you wouldn't be lying to me, would you?
-不，老板。我是说，我可能，我可能闭上眼睛一两秒钟因为我，你知道的，我太累了。
- No, boss. I mean, I-I might've-- I might've shut my eyes for a second or two as I-- you know, I was so tired.
那是一段漫长的旅程-尤斯蒂斯，嘘。
It was--it was a long ride - and I-I-- - Eustice, shh.
-值勤时睡着是一件可怕的事情。
- Falling asleep on guard duty is a terrible thing to do.
如果布里格斯出现了，而你还在睡觉呢?
What if Briggs had shown up and you'd been asleep?
是的。
Yeah.
是啊，他可能像你说的，溜进来抓了我们。
Yeah, he might have snuck in and got us, like you said.
——不!我会看到他的。
- No! I would have seen him.
嘘!嘘!
Shh! Shh!
我帮了你一个忙。
Now, I did you a favor.
好吧。
All right.
下次你值班的时候，困了，只要捏一下受伤的手指，你就会重新振作起来。
Next time you're on watch, you get a little sleepy, you just give that broken finger a squeeze, and you'll perk right back up.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
进城只有一条路。
There's only one way into town.
如果他们在下面，他们会监视每一个进来的人。
If they're down there, they'll be watching everyone who comes in.
他们在谷仓里留了言。
They left a message in the barn.
感觉很熟悉。就像它是为我而生的。
It felt familiar. Like it was meant for me.
上面说什么?
What'd it say?
我不喜欢走进来，不知道我在找谁。
I don't like walking in, not knowing who I'm looking for.
如果他们认识我，就会占上风。
If they know me, it'll give them the edge.
他们会看到我来的。
They'll see me coming.
我不会见他们的。
I won't see them.
你觉得他们会认识我吗?
Do you think they'll know me?
现在你随意地骑车进城。
Now you ride into town casually.
你从你父母的农场被派去办事。
You've been sent on an errand from your parents' farm up the road.
抬起头，仔细地看着每个人。
Keep your head up, and look at everyone carefully.
直奔商店。
Head straight for the mercantile.
进去让那个人买些东西。
Go inside and ask the man to buy something.
然后随便问一下有没有人从镇上来过。
And then casually ask if any riders had come through town.
不管他告诉你什么，你都要直接告诉我。
Whatever he tells you, you bring that information straight back to me.
我能帮你吗，小姐?
Can I help you, young lady?
年轻的女士吗?
Young lady?
请原谅我的无礼。
Pardon my manners.
你一定发现我在做白日梦。
You must have caught me daydreaming.
我差点忘了我为什么来这里。
I almost forgot why I came in here.
我妈妈昨天突然想到她要为教堂这周末的聚餐做个蛋糕。
My mama got it in her head yesterday that she had to bake a cake for the church pot luck this weekend.
去年，她做了一个派，但她用的苹果长在约翰逊先生的苹果树上，就是他屋外的那棵。
Last year, she made a pie, but the apples she used grew on Mr. Johnson's apple tree, the one back by his outhouse.
你不知道吗，那些苹果尝起来像屎一样，吃过的人都恶心到肠子里。
And wouldn't you know it, those apples tasted plum like shit and made anyone who ate 'em sick to their gut.
我跟你说，我觉得外面厕所里的东西沉入了根部改变了一个普通苹果的味道。
I tell ya, I think that shit in the outhouse sunk down into the roots and changed the way a basic apple can taste.
但约翰逊先生说那是一派胡言，正因为如此，他不让妈妈再拿苹果做苹果派了，就我而言，我和妈妈都没问题
But Mr. Johnson says that's a bunch of hooey, and because of that, he won't let Mama have any more apples for her apple pie, which, as far as I'm concerned, is fine by me and my Mama
因为就像我之前提到的，那些苹果吃起来就像屎一样。
'cuz like I mentioned before, those apples taste like shit anyhow.
约翰逊先生到底是谁?
Who the hell is Mr. Johnson?
-这是你看到的小女孩吗，Boots?
- Is this the little girl you seen, Boots?
她就是那天早上我们见到的那个小女孩。
- It is the little girl we saw the other morning.
你好，小小姐。
Hello there, little miss.
你骑的是一匹好马。
That's a fine horse you're riding.
我忍不住注意到马鞍。
Couldn't help but notice the saddle.
你不介意告诉我你是怎么拿到的吧?
Wouldn't mind telling me how you got it, would you?
更好的是……你为什么不直接告诉我你爸爸在哪里?
Better yet... why don't you just tell me where your daddy is?
玛丽亚。这是我的小妹妹。
Maria. Well, this here is my little sister.
早上好。
Buenos dias.
还是没有他的踪迹。
Still no sign of him.
嗯。
Hm.
我想他很快就会回来的。
He'll be around soon enough, I 'spect.
-这只还没吃东西呢
- This one hasn't touched her food.
-我想她是吓得不敢吃了。
- I 'spect she's too scared to eat.
对吧，小妹妹?你怕得不敢吃吗?
Right, little sister? You too scared to eat?
不。
No.
当然不是。
Of course not.
“看来科尔顿·布里格斯的女儿什么都不怕。”
'Spect daughter of Colton Briggs ain't scared of nothin.'
你们照我说的把牌子挂在外面了吗?
You boys hang that sign outside like I asked?
-红色油漆。如你所愿。
- Red paint. Just like you asked.
——好。大迈克在哪里?
- Good. Where's Big Mike?
-他在进城的路上有很好的角度。
- He's got a good angle at the road into town.
啊,好。
Ah, well.
你们其中一人在镇的另一头安家。
One of you set up at the other end of town.
另一个在街对面。
The other across the street.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
,男孩。
And, boys.
别让人看见，好吗?
Stay out of sight, all right?
在我们为他举办惊喜派对之前，他必须先到镇中心看看我们的邀请函。
It's important he gets to the middle of town and sees our invitation before we throw him his little surprise party.
-老大，如果我们有机会干掉科尔顿·布里格斯，我们应该这么做。
- Boss, if we get a chance to put a bullet in Colton Briggs, we ought to do it.
和那样的人玩游戏不明智。
It ain't smart playing games with a fella like that.
-听起来他才是害怕的那个
- Sounds like he's the one who's scared.
当然，不是吗?
Sure does, doesn't it?
你听到小妹妹说什么了吗?
You hear what little sister said?
你害怕吗?
You scared?
-我去镇的另一头。
- I'll take the other end of town.
老板随时都在等布里格斯。
Boss is expecting Briggs anytime.
你最好醒醒。
Might wanna wake your ass up.
我醒了。
I'm awake.
——好。-保持这样。
- Good. - Keep it that way.
我们应该在杀他之前先让他进城。
We're supposed to let him get into town before we kill him.
想让他看到我们抓住了他女儿什么的。
Wants him to see that we got his daughter or something.
是有意义的。
Makes sense.
-这对你自己和我们大家都有好处。
- You do yourself and all of us a favor.
你要是看到那个狗娘养的，就一枪崩了他。
You see that son of a bitch, you put a bullet in him.
你好!
Hi-ya!
回到那里去……
Go back right there...
-如果你不是太害怕吃东西，为什么你还不碰你的食物?
- If you ain't too scared to eat, why ain't you touched your food yet?
可能是毒药。
It's probably poison.
-所以你害怕了。害怕毒药。
- So you is scared. Scared of poison.
-你不必害怕不吃毒药。
- You don't have to be scared to not eat poison.
只是不傻。
Just not stupid.
看到了吗?
You see this?
没有毒。
No poison.
就算我想，我也下不了毒。
I couldn't poison even if I wanted to.
我想毒害你的亲人是一种罪过。
Reckon it's some kind of sin to poison your kin.
别再说了。
Stop saying that.
别再说什么了?
Stop sayin' what?
别叫我你妹妹。
Stop calling me your sister.
我们不是亲戚。
We ain't kin.
你和我几乎在所有方面都是亲戚。
You and I are most certainly kin in almost all respects.
这是你父亲的劳动成果，绝对没问题。
The, uh, fruits of your father's labors, sure as shootin'.
你是个骗子。
You're a liar.
-我不是说你爸爸把我妈妈肚子搞大，然后生了个孩子。
- I'm not saying that your daddy knocked my mama up and they made a baby.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
还有另外一个男人，他有幸拥有我的肉身出生。
There was another man who had the honors of my physical birth.
但他已经不在了。
But he's not around no more.
鉴于这一天我想把我的…“精神。”
On account of the day I like to call my... "spiritual birth."
你看，就是在那天，你爸爸…他觉得我不再需要我的了。
You see, it was on that day that your daddy... Well, he decided I didn't need mine anymore.
他把他从我身边带走了。就在我面前。
He took him away from me. Right there in front of me.
我看着他死去。
I watched him die.
看着生命离开他的眼睛。
Watched the life leave his eyes.
就在那时，我凝视着杀死他的人的眼睛。
It was right then that I stared into the eyes of the man who killed him.
你知道你爸爸做了什么吗?
And you know what your daddy did?
他也瞪着我。
He stared right back at me.
然后他……他骑上马走了。
Then he... he got on his horse and he rode away.
但不是他的全部。不。
But not all of him. No.
看,他……他把自己的一小部分深深地埋在了我的身体里。就像一粒种子。
See, he... he left a tiny little piece of himself buried deep inside of me. Like a seed.
我在想一个保险政策。
Workin' on a little insurance policy.
我们可不想让那些小子想到带着钱跑路。
We don't need those boys gettin' any ideas about running off with the money.
以前我在这一带除了龙舌兰酒什么都找不到。
It used to be I couldn't find nothing around these parts except tequila.
在圣罗莎找到威士忌?
Finding whiskey in Santa Rosa?
它的进步。
It's progress.
你看，进步的问题在于有些东西必须被舍弃。
You see, the problem with progress is that something's gotta go.
新进旧出。
In with the new, out with the old.
这就是世界之道。
That's the way of the world.
但是这种转变……哦，很少有和平的。
But this transition... oh, it's rarely a peaceful one.
不,女士。
No, ma'am.
权力交接是一种暴力。
Transition of power is one of violence.
必要的暴力。
Necessary violence.
这就是我们今天在这里的原因。
Which is why we're here today.
你看，我体内有个怪物。
You see, I got a monster inside of me.
魔鬼本身。
The devil himself.
只要世上还有一个恶魔，那个恶魔就无法逃脱。
That devil can't get out while there's another devil out there in the world.
这两个恶魔不可能同时存在。
Both these devils can't exist at the same time.
哦，我明白了。
Oh, I get it.
你疯了。
You're crazy.
不过别担心，我父亲很快就会来。
But don't worry, my father will be here soon.
他会解决的。
He'll fix that.
嗯，你知道，
Hmm, you know,
我很高兴我们能在一起。
I'm glad we had this time together.
像兄弟姐妹一样互相了解。
Get to know each other as siblings.
因为在今晚之后，在你父亲回来之后
'Cuz after tonight, after your father gets here...
我要做你的新爸爸了。
well, I'm gonna be your new daddy.
我们看看有什么需要修理。
And we'll see what needs fixin'.
尤斯蒂思!
Eustice!
啊，他来了。
Agh, he's here.
尤斯蒂思!
Eustice!
他在这里!
He's here!
的帮助!
Help!
他在这里。
He's here.
别，先生，求你了，别杀
Don't, mister, please, don't kill--
天呐
Holy shit.
他在这里!他杀了大迈克，还抓了一个墨西哥牛仔!
He's here! He done killed Big Mike, and got one of them Mexican cowboys!
魔鬼是不会让人失望的。
- The devil does not disappoint.
我们去看爸爸吧。
Let's go see Pa.
走路。
Walk.
-他去了那栋楼后面的小巷
- He went down that alley behind these buildings.
绕过去把他引出来
Go around and flush him out.
基督全能的。
Christ Almighty.
-尤斯蒂斯，你听到我说什么了吗?
- Eustice, did you hear what I said?
走吧!
Go!
我抓住你了，蠢货。
I got you, pendejo.
你看到他了吗?
You see him?
-他肯定绕回来了
- He must've circled back.
我抓到他了!
I got him!
他抓住了布茨，但我射中了他!
He got Boots, but I shot him!
他死了吗?
Is he dead?
不。我只是用翅膀打他。
No. I only winged him.
但我一枪就打中了他。
But I got a bullet in him, sure as shit.
他躲在巷子边的那栋楼里。
He's holed up in that building over there by the alley.
你确定吗?
You sure about that?
他像是那种会躲起来等我们来抓他的人吗?
He seem like the type of fella to just hole up and wait for us to come get him?
我们走着瞧吧。
Guess we'll see.
你们两个，你们去看那个商品。
You two, you see that mercantile.
现在，杀死你兄弟的恶棍就在里面。
Now, the villain that killed your buddy is inside.
你为什么不进去把他叫来?
Why don't you go in there and get him?
如果你能把他活着带出来，我就给你双倍报酬。
I'll double your pay if you bring him out alive.
现在小心点。他是个狡猾的家伙。
Be careful now. He's a snake.
他也许是条蛇，但他不是该死的巫师。
He may be a snake but he ain't a goddamn wizard.
尤斯蒂思。
Eustice.
我需要你相信我。
I need you to just trust me.
你能做到吗?
Can you do that?
真遗憾在快结束的时候让你走了。
Shame to have to let you go so close to the end.
布里格斯!
Briggs!
我叫你出来。
I'm calling you out.
你们以前不就是这么干的吗?
Ain't that what you boys used to do?
叫对方出来。
Call each other out.
在街上解决你们的分歧。
Settle your differences in the street.
我们还是老办法吧!
Let's do this the old way!
把枪套上，先生。
Holster that pistol, mister.
我发誓我会杀了这个小女孩。
I swear to God I'll kill this little girl.
你好,英俊的。
Hello, handsome.
还记得我吗?
Remember me?
不。
No.
举起手来。
Get your hands up.
两个都是。
Both of 'em.
它是破产。
It's busted.
-你抓到他了，老大-我们该怎么办?
- You got him, boss. - What are we gonna do?
你真的不记得我了。
You really don't remember me.
我得说，伤害了我的感情。
I gotta say, hurts my feelings.
但我想这并不奇怪。
But I guess it's not too surprising.
上次你见我的时候，我只是有点大醉。
I was just a little whooper last time you saw me.
重要的是，我记得你。
The important thing is, I remember you.
别担心。我很好。
Don't worry. I'm okay.
-我记得你，科尔顿·布里格斯
- I definitely remember you, Colton Briggs.
每次我闭上眼睛，我都能看到你的脸，盯着我。
Every time I close my eyes, I see your face, staring me down.
我闻到了你枪里的烟味，听到了我爸爸死时发出的声音。
I smell the smoke from your guns, hear the noises my daddy made as he died.
这就是我们在这里的原因。
And that's why we're here.
你,我……你的小女儿。
You, me... your little girl.
她从不告诉我她的名字，但这无关紧要。
She never would tell me her name, but it don't matter none.
我们就是一个幸福的大家庭。
We're just one big happy family.
你看，我们要摊牌了，你和我。
You see, we're gonna have a showdown, you and me.
然后你就有机会一枪崩了我就像你对我爸爸那样。
And you get the opportunity to put a bullet in my head just like you did my daddy.
如果你这么做，尤斯蒂斯会一枪崩了你女儿的头。
And if you do that, Eustice here, he's gonna blow your little girl's head off.
老大，杀了他。
Boss, just kill him.
闭嘴。
Shut up.
现在…你杀了我，看着你女儿死。
Now... you kill me, and watch your little girl die.
或者救你女儿，看着我取代你的位置。
Or save your daughter, and watch me take your place.
布鲁克。
Brooke.
我有我需要的一切。
I have all I need.
请注意，我是有人照料的。
See that I'm tended to.
不。
No.
我爱你。
And I love you.
不!
No!
天呐
Holy shit.
我做到了。
I did it.
我杀了他!
I killed him!
我很抱歉，爸爸。
I'm so sorry, Daddy.
我太爱你了。
I love you so much.
-我做到了!-真抱歉。
- I did it! - I'm so sorry.
我杀了科尔顿·布里格斯。
I killed Colton Briggs.
我杀了他。
I killed him.
听到了吗，爸爸?
You hear that, Daddy?
我杀了他。
I killed him.
这是……
It's...
这是你的。
It's you.
你才是怪物。
You're the monster.
你不是我的亲戚。
You're no kin.
布鲁克……你的母亲。
Brooke... your mother.
她会告诉你该怎么做。
She'll tell you what to do.
你活着吗?
You alive?
在后面的巷子里又发现了一具尸体
- Found another body in the back alley back there.
那就有四个了。
That makes four of 'em.
和我预期的差不多。
More or less what I expected.
把尸体集合起来，我们把他们带回来。
Round up the bodies and let's get 'em back.
他们会把他带回家吗?
Will they bring him home?
是的，我想他们会的。
Yeah, I suppose they will.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
元帅吗?
Marshal?
你打算怎么跟他们说?
What are you going to tell them?
我想为你和你爸爸的所作所为把你抓起来。
I thought I might bring you in for what you and your daddy did.
告诉他们你是如何抓住我们，折磨我们然后把我们丢在沙漠里等死。
Tell them how you captured us and tortured us and left us to die out in the desert.
但我想法官只会说你是听从了你爸爸的命令对你妈妈被杀的事怒不可遏，尽管你我都知道那不是真的。
But I suppose the judge would just say that you were following your daddy's orders and blind with rage over your mama's murder-- even though you and I both know that ain't quite true.
那样的话，你爸爸就会以罪犯的身份下葬。
And in that case, your daddy would be buried as a criminal.
然后你回到家想着怎么处理你爸爸的店。
And you would go home to try to figure out what to do with your daddy's store.
-在酒吧发现了一个保险箱，法警
- Found a strongbox in the saloon, Marshal.
-干得好，下士。就是这些了。
- Good work, Corporal. That'll be all.
然后我想告诉他们你和你爸爸一起来了，你给我的警官做了肩部手术救了他一命。
And then I considered telling them that you and your daddy came along, and you saved my deputy's life by performing field surgery on his shoulder.
然后你继续追查杀害你母亲的凶手然后他在逮捕他们的过程中被杀了这样你就可以回家了。
Then you proceeded to track down your mother's murderers and then he was killed in the process of their apprehension in which case you would still go home.
所以我想既然这两种情况的结果是一样的，我更喜欢不涉及我被一个12岁女孩抓住的故事。
So I figure since the outcomes in both those scenarios are the same, I prefer the story that doesn't involve me getting captured by a 12-year-old girl.
也许在那个版本中，我们也可以忘记那个坚固的盒子。
And maybe in that version, we can forget all about that strong box too.
在那个版本中……
In that version...
我爸爸能成为英雄吗?
my daddy gets to be a hero?
作为交换，你要谨慎行事是的。
In exchange for your discretion... Yes.
-我想这听起来是对的。
- I believe that sounds about right.
那就这么定了。
Well then, it's decided.
元帅吗?
Marshal?
找到你的马了吗?
Did you find your horse?
被绑在镇边上了。
Tied up at the edge of town.
就像他说的。
Just like he said.
回家去吧，小布里格斯。
You get on home, little Briggs.
照顾好你爸爸的店。
Take care of your daddy's store.
丫!
Ya!
听到了吗，爸爸?
You hear that, Daddy?
你会成为英雄的。
You're gonna be a hero.
妈妈会很骄傲的。
Mama would be so proud.
玛丽亚，是吗?
Maria, isn't it?
是的,小姐。
Si, Senorita.
-你去酒馆里把我哥哥的鞍囊拿来给我好吗?
- Why don't you fetch me my brother's saddlebag from inside the saloon?